麦克斯 卡洛琳 我有事情要宣布
Max, Caroline, I have announcement.
你是因为踩着高跷 才有这样的身高吗
You're actually much shorter and are walking on stilts?
我为明天的情人节晚餐
I have made a special menu
阿憨 真是浪漫啊
Han, that's so romantic.
没错 既浪漫又白目
Yeah, romantic and wrong.
这地方不是在演《当哈里遇见萨莉》
This place isn't When Harry met Sally.
而是"当哈里遇见沙门氏菌"
It's "When Harry met Salmonella."
麦克斯 总会三明治
Max, Club Sandwich.
先提醒你 我有个创可贴下落不明
And heads up... I lost a band-aid.
有主题菜单 我就能合理抬高价格
Theme menu means I can charge one bigger price,
就像高档餐厅那样
like in top restaurants.
看见没 "套子定价"
See? "Prick fix."
阿憨呀 这个应该念"套餐定价"
Oh, Han, it's pronounced "prix fixe."
你瞧见咱们主厨了吗
Have you seen our chef?
铁定是念"套子定价"
It's definitely "prick fix."
明天晚上
Tomorrow night,
丘比特会飞来威廉斯堡餐馆哟
Cupid will come to Williamsburg diner.
懒得告诉他其实丘比特早死了
Didn't have the heart to tell him Cupid is dead.
没错 他在飞过高速公路时
Yep, hit by a mack truck
被一辆重型卡车撞得稀巴烂
crossing the Brooklyn-Queens expressway...
他那裹着尿布的婴儿肥臀
His fat, diapered baby ass
溅满整个挡风玻璃
splattered all over the windshield.
我爱情人节
I love Valentine's Day.
你就这反应啊 姐杀了丘比特呢
That's your reaction? I killed Cupid.
无论你有无浪漫情怀
You're either romantic or not.
我都懒得花力气去说服你
I'm not even going to try to convince you.
他的确死了 证据就是...
Oh, he's dead. And the proof...
你上一次见人坠入爱河是什么时候
When's the last time you knew anyone who fell in love?
真爱哦 好比《冰冰爱可可》
Real love, like Ice Loves Coco.
那他俩呢
How about them?
他们整晚都拉着手 浪漫地耳语
They've been holding hands and romantic whispering all night.
他们的浪漫耳语其实是
Their romantic whispering goes like this.
"我有乳头夹"
"I own nipple clamps."
咻 丘比特没死
Plink! Cupid's not dead.
咻咻 爱神之箭飞射过去
Plink! There goes his little arrow.
咻咻咻
Plink, plink!
我夹 哎呦 我夹 哎呦
Clamp, ouch! Clamp, ouch!
我夹夹夹 我爽爽爽
Clamp, clamp! Ouch, ouch!
麦克斯 既然十二点已过
Max, since it's just after midnight,
现在就算是情人节啦
it's now officially Valentine's Day.
我这里给你准备了点东西 你猜是什么呀
I've got something in here for you... guess what it is.
从你脸上的淫笑判断
Well, judging from that smile on your face,
我猜是你的围裙里面有个手指宽的"洞"
I'd say it's a finger-sized hole in your apron.
心型糖果 来 把手伸出来
Candy hearts! Here, hold out your hand.
咱们来尝点甜头
Let's get our heart on.
我的"头"早就准备就绪
I'm way ahead of you.
"做我的爱人" 真经典 你的是什么
"Be mine"... classic. What's yours say?
"卡洛琳·钱宁逊爆了
"Caroline Channing is lame.
我讨厌你给我糖
"I hate you for giving me this.
情人节去死吧"
Valentine's Day is the worst."
哇 肉桂味的
Ooh, cinnamon. Mmm.
晚上好 厄尔
Good evening, Earl.
天啊 天啊 苏菲
My, my, my, Sophie,
香衣配美人 我心跳加速难自持
seeing you in that dress makes my heart race.
腰肢如竹子 胸前结椰子
Two scoops of ice cream in a one scoop cone.
厄尔 你真会逗我开心
Oh, Earl, you make me smile.
波兰要是能多点黑人就好了
I wish we had black people in Poland when I was growing up.
是很可惜 咱们黑人肯定会喜欢
Too bad. We really would have enjoyed
种族隔离与希特勒呢
segregation and Hitler.
你们好呀 邻居们
Oh, hi, building neighbors.
我刚好开车经过 看到正在下雨
Well, I was just driving by, and since it was raining,
就想说用我的加长轿车
I thought I could offer you two girls
送你们俩妹子回家
a ride home in my town car.
上次有人说要送我回家
The last time someone offered me a ride,
结果我被扔进新泽西的下水道
I ended up in a drainage pipe in Jersey.
苏菲 你租了辆加长轿车吗
Sophia, you rent a town car?
对啊 不过只有在下雨的时候
Yes, but only when it's raining,
你看 我去做了接发 接指甲
because, you know, I got hair extensions and nail extensions,
所以我..."接着"就不屑走路了
and, you know, I... I'm too extended to walk.
你好
Hello.
我从厨房里看见你
I saw you from kitchen.
你让上菜口变得如诗如画
You turned pick-up window into painting.
咻
Plink!
吧台上的裸体绒画
Velvet painting of nude at counter.
我夹 哎呦
Clamp, ouch!
那俩姑娘说你有一家清洁公司
The girls tell me you own cleaning service.
我想请你来打扫我家
I would like to hire you to clean my house.
没错 这个可以有
Oh, yeah, this is possible.
我会叫个姑娘去 你的地址是哪里
I will send girl. What is your address?
我不要别的姑娘
I don't want some girl.
我就要你来打扫
I want you to come clean.
想我来 你没那本事
Oh, you cannot get me to come.
我当然有本事让你"来"[高潮]
Oh, I can get you to come.
不可能 我不上门[来高潮]很久了
No, I can no longer come anymore.
算了 麦克斯和卡洛琳可以来
No, Max and Caroline can come.
不 不 我们才不来
No, no, we're not coming.
所以没人能让你"来"[高潮]吗
So no one can get you to come?
当然 有些人可以让我"来"
Well, some people can get me to come...
但不是你
Just not you.
傲娇难泡 我喜欢
Hard to get... I like it.
你去拿外套 我去结账
Go get the coats. I'll get this check.
这是最后一笔单子了 厄尔
Here's the last check, Earl.
麦克斯 你能帮我入下帐吗
Oh, Max, can you take care of that for me, please?
可以 为什么
Sure. Why?
没什么急事 就是心脏病发而已
Uh, nothing pressing... Just having a heart attack.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
慢着 你心脏病发了
Wait, you're having a heart attack?
确定肯定及一定
Most definitely.
我这辈子病发过三次 跟老朋友一样熟
I've had three in my life. We're old friends.
厄尔 你可是心脏病病发呀
Earl, you're having a heart attack.
没事的 你看见我的橘子了吗
I'll be fine. Have you seen my tangerine?
我特意留个橘子 准备回家路上吃
I had a tangerine set aside for my walk home.
别管那橘子了
Forget the tangerine.
厄尔心脏病发了
Earl's having a heart attack!
苏菲 我们得用你的轿车送他去医院
Sophie, we're taking the town car to the hospital.
厄尔 你什么时候开始疼的
Earl, when did the pain start?
我看见穿裙子的苏菲时
When I saw Sophie in that dress.
靠 不是吧
Oh, hell, no!
怎么这么多人排队 新iPhone出来了吗
Why is this line so long? Did the new iPhone come out?
咱们把他扶过去吧
Let's just get him over there.
麦克斯 你能把这些人弄走吗
Max, anything you can do to move this along?
走开 名人来了
Move! Celebrity coming through.
摩根·弗里曼心脏病发了
Morgan Freeman having a heart attack.
他心脏病发了
He is having a heart attack.
疼痛级别从一到十 你是几级
On a scale of one to ten, what's your pain?
二级 我们只是刚好经过
Uh, two, we were just in the neighborhood,
想找个地方吃果冻
looking for a place to have jell-o.
我是在问摩根·弗里曼说话
I was talking to Morgan Freeman.
现在就治他
Take him now!
先生 他有心脏病史
Sir, he has a history of heart trouble.
好吧 把他送进去
All right, we'll get him in.
厄尔 跟护士去吧
Earl, go with the nurse.
靠 居然是男护士
Damn, it's a man.
我们就在这等 厄尔
We'll be right out here, Earl.
一定会没事的
Everything is gonna be okay.
去那边坐着等吧
Have a seat and wait.
看着老娘 小弱鸡
Look at me, gingerbread.
如果他有什么三长两短
If anything happens to him,
我会用订书机 把你的阴囊钉在椅子上
I will staple your nut sack to that chair.
没错 又是我
That's right... it's me again.
都说过九遍了 他没事
For the tenth time, he's fine.
他只是轻微病发 也有人会妥善照顾
He had a minor attack, but he's in good hands.
请相信我 我在这里心脏病发过两次了
I would know... I had both of my heart attacks here.
我得亲自进去看了才放心
I want to go back there and see for myself.
只准家属进去
Family members only.
-我是他的女儿 -真的吗
- Well, I'm his daughter. - Oh, really?
病历上说他已经七十五岁了
It says here he's 75 years old...
他晚婚晚育
Well, he started late.
还是个非裔美国人
And African-American.
他跟个白鬼晚婚晚育不行啊
He started late with a honky.
我就是传说中的杂交婴儿
I'm one of those combo babies.
给
Here...
你不是要证据吗
You need proof?
我姓布莱克[黑]
My last name is Black,
看见没 麦克斯·布莱克
see? Max Black.
他是黑人 我姓黑
He's black. I'm Black.
如果我们俩不是亲人 才有鬼咧
It'd be dumb if we weren't related.
我能继续玩"愤怒的小鸟"了吗
Can I just get back to playing Angry Birds?
我此生挚爱在里面独自担惊受怕
You are yammering on here about nothing
而你除了会说废话 什么都不会
while the love of my life is back there alone and scared.
你刚说他是你的父亲
You said he was your father.
现在又成了你此生挚爱了
Now he's the love of your life?
两者皆是 我们是狂野的南方人
He's both. We're from the South.
回去坐着吧
Have a seat.
我为了买这两杯拿铁 等了好半天
I got us two lattes. It took forever.
我前面那哥儿们 为了等一杯摩卡星冰
The guy in front of me missed his kidney transplant
都错过了他的肾脏移植手术了
waiting for a mocha frappuccino.
-有新消息了吗 -没有
- Any news? - The same.
他们也不让我进去
But they won't let me back there.
我甚至说厄尔是我父亲了
I even told him Earl was my father.
机会来了 楚巴卡护士离开座位了
Now's my chance. Nurse Chewbacca's on the move.
我要偷溜进去
I'm going back there.
如果你发现有人注意到我
If you see anyone about to notice me sneak by,
就帮我把大家注意力都转移到你身上
draw all the attention to yourself.
麦克斯 我不知道我是否做得来
Max, I don't know if I can do that.
你说得对 这是我的专长
You're right. That's kind of my thing.
-好的 我想想 -没时间想了
- Okay, let me think. - You don't have time to think.
直接把咖啡扔墙上就行
Just throw the coffees against the wall.
这太离谱了
That's ridiculous.
我可是沃尔顿商学院的毕业尖子生
I graduated top of my class at Wharton.
我的本事比这大多了
I can do better than that.
呼叫本德尔医生 呼叫本德尔医生
Paging Dr. Bender. Paging Dr. Bender, please.
天啊
Oh, my God!
这咖啡居然不是脱脂的
Those were not nonfat.
厄尔
Earl!
-你在里面吗 -麦克斯 是你吗
- You in here? - Max, is that you?
你真好
Ain't you sweet?
但你不必等着我了
But you didn't have to wait around for me.
这位是小水仙
This is Narcissus.
她来自斐济群岛
She's from the Fiji Islands
刚刚帮我擦一个暴爽的澡
and gives one hell of a sponge bath.
你好 能让我们单独说句话吗
Hi. Can we have a minute alone?
厄尔 你觉得现在让人帮你"擦澡"合适吗
Earl, do you think this is a good time to have a sponge bath...
就你这虚弱的小心肝
I mean, in your condition?
麦克斯 当护士长这样时
Max, when they look like that,
擦澡没有合不合适 只有爽不爽
there's never a bad time for a sponge bath.
-那你现在没事咯 -好得很
- So are you doing okay now? - Pretty good.
医生说这次是轻微的
The doctor said it was a mild one,
但我得留院观察几个晚上
but I'm going to have to stay here a couple nights.
你能帮我问问自己住一间
Could you find out how much extra for me
要加多少钱吗
to get my own room?
单人房吗
A private room?
上次我睡在这种集体病房时
The last time I was in one of these places,
我隔壁床的家伙以为自己是鹦鹉
the guy in the bed next to me thought he was a parrot
整晚都在管我要饼干
and asked me for crackers the whole damn night.
好的 我会给你找间单人间
Done. I'll get you your own room.
别担心钱的问题
And don't worry about the expenses.
我留有点钱 以备不时之需
I got a little money stashed away for a rainy day.
我才不用你的钱呢
I am not using your money.
我猜"不时"指的是大麻的一种吧
But let me guess, "rainy day" is a strain of weed?
你果然懂我
Now you're getting it.
晚点再来看你
I'll see you later.
不许死 不然我杀了你
Don't die, or I'll kill you.
你又闹哪样 现在又想要间单人房了
So what, now you want a private room?
他怎么付得起钱呀
How's he going to pay for that?
所以那个老人是全美国唯一一个
Oh, so that old man has to be the only man in America
得自己掏腰包付医疗费的人吗
who has to pay his medical bills?
弗里曼先生演过很多成功的电影呢
Mr. Freeman's done a lot of successful movies.
我觉得你这挖苦的态度太不专业了
I don't think your sarcastic attitude is very professional.
"专业"
"Professional"?
一个小时前 你的流氓朋友恐吓我说
Um, an hour ago, your little thug friend here
要劈我一刀 把我劈出个阴道来
threatened to cut me so deep, I'd have a vagina.
我说到 就敢做到
That offer still stands.
她心情不好就会把阴道挂嘴边
She's upset. And vagina's her go-to.
我之所以没叫保安
Well, the only reason I haven't called security
是因为他们两周前被炒鱿鱼了
is they were laid off two weeks ago.
请问你的大名是
What is your name?
缇格
Tig.
是个假名 祝你好运
And it's fake, so good luck with that.
先生 你可是代表着
Sir, you're representing
薛柯特家族医院的形象
the Shecter family wing of this hospital.
我们家族认识薛柯特家族
My family knows the Schecters.
事实上 他们的儿子大卫也在这实习
In fact, their son David interns here,
如果我给他打电话 他可会不高兴哦
and if I made a call, he would not be pleased.
如果你认识他们
If you know them,
咱们干嘛还跟前台的二货废话呀
why are we talking to this lump behind a desk?
去死吧 红脸猪 我们要骑在你头上了
Suck it, red face! We're going over your head!
现在是不是气得牙痒痒呀 贱人
How do you like me now, bitch?
快打电话
Hey, get your phone.
看看他能不能给厄尔安排间单人房
See if he can swing Earl a private room.
我应该还有他的号码
I think I still have his cell number.
我们约过几次会 后来我发现他真的
We went out a few times until I realized he was serious
要走无偿服务那条路
about going down that pro Bono route.
-你们俩睡了吗 -没
- Did you two have sex? - No.
太棒了 人情债你可以肉偿了
Sweet, that's what you can offer him for the room.
真厉害
That's amazing.
居然还有花店大半夜送花上门
Someone found a florist that delivers after midnight.
这有什么厉害的
That's not so amazing.
我认识一个叫"粘得要死斯基"的家伙
I know a guy named "Sticky Icky" Ricky
专门半夜送货上门
who delivers exclusively after midnight.
我刚意识到这是我首个
You know, I just realized this is the first Valentine's Day
不会收到我父亲玫瑰的情人节
I won't get flowers from my father.
又感人又带着一如既往的乱伦恶心
Aw, that's cute, with a big old side of creepy.
不 多贴心呀
No, it's sweet.
我出生后的每一年
Every year from the time I was a baby,
即使当我有男朋友的时候
and even when I had boyfriends,
我都会收到父亲送的玫瑰 卡片上写着
I'd get flowers from my father with a card that says,
"你永远都是我的情人"
"You'll always be my Valentine."
高中时 我收到过心仪对象的情人节卡片
I got a sweet Valentine from a guy I liked in high school.
上面写着"把T恤拉起来 就给你五块钱"
It said, "I'll give you five bucks to lift your shirt."
卡洛琳 我马上过来
Caroline... Hey, I'll be right with you.
他来了 比我记忆中帅多了
There he is. Cuter than I remember.
我听到你的语音留言时 简直不敢相信
When I heard your voice mail, I couldn't believe it.
我也不是很确定 你是否愿意来见我
Yes, well, I wasn't sure you'd want to come down,
因为...你懂的
because... you know...
你两年前甩了我吗
You dumped me two years ago?
"甩"这个词有点重吧
Well, "dumped" is a strong word.
当着我的面 把我的心撕成碎片扔掉
Tore my heart out, shook it in front of my face.
这样有轻点吗
That any softer?
抱歉打断你们"强颜欢笑假客套"的对话
Hate to interrupt the "perfect white teeth" convention,
但我们赶时间
but we're in a hurry.
大卫 这是我朋友麦克斯
David, this is my friend Max.
我们的朋友入院了
A friend of ours was admitted,
希望你能帮他安排间单人房
and we were hoping to get him a private room.
所以你不是来还我
Oh, so you're not here to return
你偷走的达特茅斯大学T恤的吗
my Dartmouth t-shirt you stole from me.
是你自己送我的
You gave that to me.
才不是 我爱死那件T恤了
No, I didn't! I love that shirt.
感觉就像我离婚时失去了孩子的监护权
I feel like I lost custody of it in a divorce,
而现在反倒成了不付赡养费的爸爸了
and now I'm like a deadbeat dad.
那房间呢 能行吗
How about the room? Any chance?
拜托 求求你了
Please. Pretty please.
好吧 既然你都开口求我了
Oh, well, since you said "pretty please,"
我看看我能做点什么
I'll see what I can do.
先声明一点 我们没钱
We should be clear. We can't pay.
我们破产了 我们俩都是
We're broke... both of us.
但我相信有人跟你说了
But I'm sure you heard that somewhere.
是呀
Yeah...
大家都在说
Everywhere.
大卫 我希望我父亲没有造成
David, I hope your family didn't lose any money
你们家族的任何损失 有吗
with my father. Did they?
没有 我们仍旧富得流油
Nope, still filthy rich.
我可以行行好 分点我家的油花给你
And I can do my best to burn some filthy off that rich,
帮你朋友弄间贵宾房
by getting your friend a V.I.P. room.
跟人报几个名字
I'll just drop some names.
其实 是报我自己的名字
By that, I mean my own.
应该就能搞定
Shouldn't be a problem.
我爱犹太人
I love Jews.
没错 我们慷慨大方 麻烦广而告之
Yeah, we're generous. Spread the word.
可以的话 记得告诉小水仙我的去向
Uh, if you wouldn't mind giving Narcissus my whereabouts?
我推你经过前台时 看见那二货
Did you see the look on that desk lump's big, red face
他又肥又红的脸上的表情吗
when I pushed you by him?
看见了 但我觉得对他伸中指
I did, but I think throwing him the finger
有点小小的过分了哦
was a tad out of line.
哇 大卫医生真是说到做到呀
Wow, Dr. David really hooked us up.
是呀 感觉就像美剧里的重症监护病房一样
Yeah, this is like an episode of Cribs I.C.U. Edition.
厄尔 你觉得怎么样
So, Earl, what do you think?
上帝呀 那是马蒂斯的作品吗
Good lord, is that a Matisse?
-是吧 -亲娘咧 我到家了
- I believe so. - Then, mama, I'm home.
给 女士们 把这俩棒棒糖放进你的围裙里
Here, ladies, put these suckers in your station.
等会说不定有情人节夜的二次就餐高峰期
I think I might get a late Valentine dinner crowd.
你还觉得你可能会迎来身高二次发育呢
You also think you might get a late growth spurt,
但这两样都是不可能的
but that's not happening either.
最多会有三个单身女人
At best, you'll get three single girls
半夜踉跄地走进来 边痛哭流涕边吃木薯
waddling over at midnight to cry into some tapioca.
的确 我还是别骗自己了
True. I need to cut the crap.
情人节大餐梦破碎
Valentine's dinner is bust.
瞧 我牺牲了我的男子气概 却无半点盈利
And look, I have sacrificed my manhood for no cash value.
可你的翅膀好可爱哟
But your wings are adorable.
没错 但成套的内裤让我的"小弟们"憋死了
Yes, but matching panties are suffocating the boys.
好啦 早点关门得了
Come on, close early.
我们只有一桌暮光脑残粉
We've only got one table of twi-hards.
我想去看厄尔
I want to go see Earl.
好吧 我也爱我的兄弟厄尔
Oh, what the hell? I love my man Earl, too.
不管了 我们飞过去吧
So screw it. Let's fly over there.
这里跟波兰的医院真不一样
Ooh, this isn't like the hospitals in Poland.
灯居然都会亮耶
The lights are working.
好了 坐下吧 我每次带一个人进去
Okay, sit down. I'll take you in one at a time.
来 丘比特 你先来
All right, Cupid, you're first.
别吵醒他 快出去
Oh, don't wake him. Go back out.
天使 天啊 不要啊
Angels. Oh, lord, no.
幸好是你 阿憨
Thank God it's you, Han.
我刚看见翅膀 还以为天堂
I saw the wings, and I thought heaven was filled
全都是矮胖的中国天使 还没有爵士乐
with chunky Chinese cherubs and no jazz.
好 太棒了 五分钟后见
Oh, okay, great. I'll see you in five.
我约了大卫医生
I'm gonna go meet Dr. David.
等下
Oh, wait a second.
如果你要去见男人 你得来点唇彩
If you're going to go meet man, you need lip gloss.
谢谢 苏菲
Oh, thanks, Sophie.
别 别 别 好吧
Oh, no, no, no, no. Okay.
我有份情人节礼物要送你
I have Valentine gift I want to give you.
丙型肝炎吗
Oh, hepatitis "C"?
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day.
看看我 再看看自己
Look at me. Now look at you.
再来看看我
Now look at me again.
你觉得合适吗 搭吗
Does this look right to you?
傲娇难泡 我喜欢
Hard to get... I like it.
你的朋友怎么样了
Oh, hey. So how's your friend doing?
很好 贵宾房的事谢谢你
Good. And thanks for that V.I.P. room.
他过得像个百万富翁 我相信得花不少钱吧
He feels like a million bucks, which I'm sure is what it costs,
所以我给你带了份谢礼
so I brought you a little thank-you gift.
这不是我的达特茅斯T恤
That is not my Dartmouth shirt.
对 那件衣服还被关押在别墅里呢
No, that's held hostage at the townhouse.
这件上面写着"威廉斯堡" 我现在住那里
This says Williamsburg. That's where I live now.
不是吧 我也住那里
No way. That's where I live.
我最初搬去那里是为了气我的父亲
Yeah, I moved there just to piss my father off,
但我后来爱上了那里
but I wound up loving it.
我后来也爱上了那里
I wound up loving it, too.
我们有时间可以见个面...
Hey, maybe we could see each other there sometime...
约个会什么的呀
You know, go out?
别想了
Yeah, I don't think so.
抱歉 你刚说什么
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, what?
听着 卡洛琳
Look, Caroline,
能重遇你真的很开心 但...
it's been really great getting to reconnect with you, but...
我们之间爱火重燃是不可能的
I don't see this happening again.
我父母肯定不同意
I mean, it's my parents.
你父亲蹲大牢 丑闻满天飞
With your father in prison, the whole scandal,
我永远也不能带你回家
I could never bring you home.
当是气你父亲也不行吗
Not even just to piss off your father?
我跟卡洛琳·钱宁约会
I mean, me dating Caroline Channing...
人们会怎么想啊
What would people think?
希望你能明白我的难处
I hope you understand.
对了 谢谢你的T恤
Oh, hey, thanks for the tee.
大家都过来看我 真好
Nice of everyone to stop by.
没看见卡洛琳 她今晚很忙吗
Didn't see Caroline. She busy tonight?
没事 她就在这儿呢
Oh, no, she's here.
她在外面忙乎
She's out there running around,
想跟那个给咱们搞了间贵宾房的
trying to swing a boyfriend situation with her doctor friend
那个医生朋友重燃爱火呢
who got us the V.I.P. hook-up.
那你呢 麦克斯
What about you, Max?
在情人节也没个情人
No sweetheart on Valentine's Day.
我担心你
I worry about you.
如果你有心仪对象 要对他好一点嘛
Be nice if you had someone special.
现在不就是吗
I already do.
麦克斯 我就只剩三四十年可以活了
Ah, Max, I'm only going to be around another 30 or 40 years.
你最好把网撒大一点
You better widen the net a bit.
探视时间到 友人请离开
Visiting hours are up. Friends have to leave.
她可以留下 她是家人
She can stay, nurse. She's family.
厄尔 我是家人吗
Earl, I'm family?
对 最好的那种家人
Yes, and the best kind of family.
你不会图我的钱
You don't want my money.
厄尔 你气色好多了
Hey, Earl. You look really good.
你跟大卫医生有在医院的衣橱里开搞吗
So did you and Dr. Dave do it in a hospital closet?
就跟《实习医生格雷》里的套路一样
All very "Grey's Monotony"?
没有 我们不可能了
No, that won't be happening.
我约他出去 他说他不可能跟我约会
I asked him out and he said he could never date me,
因为我的父亲 还说"人们会怎么想"这种话
because of my father and quote "what would people think?"
什么 你说什么
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, what?
我感觉好像被撞死丘比特
I feel like I was just hit
那辆重型卡车碾过一样
by the same mack truck that killed Cupid.
现在有人真要被卡车撞了
Well, somebody's about to get hit by a truck...
麦克斯超大型卡车
A Max truck.
喂 就是你 我不记得你名字医生
Hey, you, Dr. I-Forget-Your-Name.
怎么可能 我的名字随处可见
How? It's written on every wall.
好吧 出口医生
Okay, Dr. Exit.
你有什么毛病
What is wrong with you?
医生不是都很善解人意的嘛
Doctors are supposed to be sensitive.
今天是情人节 她一无所有
I mean, it's Valentine's Day, and she has nothing.
你就不能像其他男人那样
Couldn't you be like every other guy on the planet
先哄她上她 隔天再断绝联系吗
and just lead her on and not call her the next day?
这才是得体的做法
That is the decent thing to do.
顺便告诉你一声 心型糖果让她昏了头
And for the record, she is so hopped up on candy hearts,
你今晚本可以尝到"甜头"的 真的
you would have gotten some tonight, fo' sho!
你刚犯下了这辈子最大的错误
You just made the biggest mistake of your life.
我猜你比任何人都了解我
Well, I guess nobody knows me better than you,
这位素未谋面的姑娘
girl I've never met before.
现在我想跟做无偿服务的那个你谈谈
And now I would like to speak to the pro bono part of you,
他会理解我刚才说的话
who understands that nothing I just said
不会去迁怒贵宾房里的那个人
should affect that man in the V.I.P. room.
你帮我们安排病房的行为 的确很酷
That was actually a very cool thing to do.
厄尔没事 别担心
Earl is fine. Don't worry.
至于卡洛琳的部分 抱歉
And as far as Caroline goes, I'm sorry, but...
可她的父亲伤害了很多人
Her father hurt a lot of people.
善有善报 恶有恶报
Whatever you put out there comes back to you.
又怎么了
What now...
你又想恐吓我 要把我的乳头塞我嘴里吗
you gonna threaten to feed me my nipples again?
不是
No.
其实是因为刚才有人说
Actually, someone just said something
善有善报 恶有恶报
about the things you do coming back to you,
所以我决定应该放聪明点来跟你道歉
and I decided the smart move was to apologize.
多谢 但没必要
Thanks, but it's not necessary.
其实你是今晚我碰过对我最好的人了
Actually, you're the nicest person I've dealt with tonight.
苦差事啊 伙计
Ugh. Rough job, dude.
给 情人节快乐
Here, Happy Valentine's Day.
你想找个时间出来坐坐吗
You want to go out sometime?
我干嘛要...
Why would...
好啊 号码给我 我明天打给你
Yeah, give me your number. I'll call you tomorrow.
在医院的椅子上睡一整夜
Sleeping in that hospital chair all night
也没那么难受嘛
wasn't that uncomfortable.
对 椅子还好
No, the chairs weren't.
让人难受的是 你的情人节啜泣
Your sad Valentine whimpering was.
-你今天早上感觉好点了吗 -好多了
- So how you feeling this morning? - Pretty good,
鉴于我撑过了没有父亲送花的
considering I survived the very first Valentine's Day
第一个情人节
I didn't get flowers from my father.
所以你度过了首个无爱的一年嘛
So you got one year under your belt.
别太骄傲
Don't get so cocky.
你还有二十三年才能追平我呢
You still have to make 23 more to tie me.
一直以来 我都为你觉得惋惜
You know, all this time, I've been feeling sorry for you
因为你不认识自己的父亲
'cause you didn't know your father,
但看见你对厄尔悉心照料后
but after seeing how you took care of Earl...
我为你父亲不认识自己的女儿而惋惜
I feel sorry for your father that he didn't know you.
你会是一个好女儿
You would have been a wonderful daughter.
千万别这么想
Don't hold that thought.
没坐到木薯粉前 我可不哭
I don't want to cry till after we break open the tapioca.
不是的 我没获得选美比赛冠军
No, I didn't just win a beauty contest.
这些是我在前门楼梯上发现的
No, these were left on the front doorstep.
都是送给卡洛琳的
They're both addressed to Caroline.
-抱歉 麦克斯 -没关系
- Sorry, Max. - Oh, no, that's cool.
这样我才能保持"连续无花记录"
Wouldn't want to break my winning streak.
你可以这么想嘛
Oh, well, just look at it this way.
花是她的 我是你的
She got the flowers. You got the knockers.
好啦 姑娘们
All right, girls,
我得去买痒痒挠了
well, I'm off to buy scratchers
不然都被波多黎各人买走了
before all the Puerto Ricans get them.
"你永远都是我的情人
"You'll always be my Valentine.
爱你的爸爸"
Love, Daddy."
另一束是大卫医生送的吗
The other one from Dr. Dave?
在我撕碎他的心后 改变心意了吗
Change his mind after I tore him a new one?
也是我父亲送的 不过是给你的
It's from my father as well, but it's written to you.
"谢谢你对我的宝贝照顾有加
"Thank you for taking such good care of my sweetheart.
马丁·钱宁"
M. Channing."
真贴心
That is so sweet.
男人送的玫瑰花
Roses from a man.
现在我算懂了
Now I'm starting to get it.
如果我说我想跟你老爸上床 会很怪吗
Is it weird that I kind of want to have sex with your dad?
咻
Plink!